(Yin Jisheng)
(Zheng Liyu)
"Thunderstorm"
Hi one photo
How are you doing during this time?
I'm having a bad time
Hi
I'm having a good time
What about you?
(Uncle’s 49th death anniversary)
Zhenghan
why did you come here
I feel like you're going to be here today
Unexpectedly
Encountered by chance
That is to say
Are you here to see my dad?
Yeah
thank you
Although he is your father, he is also my uncle
(so Xu Zhenhe)
Sorry dad
It's been so long since I came to see you
Your face looks haggard
Really?
Dark circles are also heavy
Because I didn't sleep well
Where is the company?
Don't do this
I can't do anything because you're not here
It was always like this in the beginning
That person seems to be my whole world
How can anyone disappear so quietly?
You'd better get rid of this bad habit
Bad habit of running away from home without saying a word
This is the first time
Am I not your partner?
Of course we have to solve the problem together
You ran away from me, what should I do?
I'm on your side
I was really shocked
You don’t answer the phone either
Even if I want to find you
There is no other way
No matter how angry you are after that
Don't do this either
i will be better to you
Don't be angry, okay?
I didn't leave because I was angry
I left because I didn't want to see you
To break up with you
Did you get a lot of money from my dad?
Of course I have to get more.
I will return it
Those things are not important at all
are you okay
How are you doing?
Yeah
Still able to hold on
Lie
You'll be fine soon too
Wait for time to pass
You will also feel that you can endure it
Is there any way you can live without seeing me for the rest of your life?
Big bad guy
It's not that simple
you also know
I am a simple-minded person.
Once we break up, I won't look back
Are we really done with this?
Is this how it ends?
Yeah
One photo…
I don't want to break up
I already said
I don't want to see you
Being with you makes me miserable
One photo…
I don't want to be with you anymore
I'm leaving
Your call will be forwarded to voicemail
Billing starts after the beep
how are you doing
I miss you so much
Just one more year…
Just keep dating me for one more year.
One photo
One photo…
where are you
I'm dying
Zhenghan
One photo
Why are you like this?
It's really distressing
Even if I'm not here, you still have to live a good life.
I can't even sleep well
Can't even breathe
can you come back
Hello Xu Zhenghan
cheer up
Hello
Damn it
There are a lot of tricks on you
Have you been to the hospital?
Take it by hand
How
Do you think I'm chilling?
Is it ridiculous?
I also think I'm ridiculous
Feel free to laugh at me
What's the big deal about breaking up?
how do you know
With your character, I can tell you are the one who was dumped.
I'm not over yet
He himself wants to end the trouble there
selfish guy
So
What was his reason for breaking up?
Countless
are you crying
No
I just yawned
Oh, you loser, you still say "countless"
I'm not crying, you bastard
One photo
He came to our hospital yesterday
So what
His new date is quite gentle
Come with him every time
No matter what time it is
who is
That tall, white guy?
Yeah
That piece of shit Zhang Xiuxiao
What's going on
what
what happened to you
how do you know
You called me early yesterday morning
I kept crying 'Yizhao', don't you remember?
Damn it
Damn, so embarrassing
Do you know you are embarrassed and still act like this?
so
When is the next visit for Yi Zhao?
hello
This is for you
Americano coffee, okay?
I don't know what you like to drink
thank you
Are you a friend of the dean?
I've seen you several times
Yes
Today…
There are no patients
Yes, yes
Hello Xu Zhenghan
You are really here
Alas, it’s really the saint of love
I have no idea what you're talking about
What don’t you understand?
I'm sick
waste
- Damn it. - Go get an IV drip and then go home.
Donne, please give him an intravenous drip.
good
-Please come here. -Okay.
Please try to make the drip flow as slow as possible
That might take an hour. Is that okay?
Okay, you can rest
Hello do you have an appointment?
Yes
The name is…
Li Yizhao
Okay, you can go in directly
You go in for a consultation. I'll sit here and wait for you.
Mr. Zhenghan, do you have any questions?
The needle seemed to fall off while sleeping
I'll help you do it again. Please come here.
No need
Repair effect
Let's go home quickly
Where do you want to go?
get out of the way
Damn you, how dare you lie to me
When I want you to leave with dignity
Just disappear from my sight
What does it have to do with you?
Do you really not know about Yizhao being threatened?
Does it really have nothing to do with you?
Threat?
Not Zhenghan
Really
Xu Zhengyin’s foul mouth said this guy’s name
please
what does that mean
I don't care if you know it or not
As long as you are around, if you take a picture, you will always be unhappy
Let's go first, okay?
Do you really not know about Yizhao being threatened?
Does it really have nothing to do with you?
Xu Zhengyin’s foul mouth said this guy’s name
Xu Zhengyin…
God my relatives
What brings you here?
Are you going to punch me again?
do you have medicine
Medicine?
do you want it
Yeah
What can I give you?
Ecstasy, cocaine, or…
alprazolam
Wait
Where is the medicine?
But why do you suddenly want to take drugs?
Ah Li Yizhao
But that guy's not on drugs, dammit.
I stuffed it into his mouth and didn’t even eat it.
Still refuse to let me touch
Found it
Is this enough?
OK
Since you are a relative, I will give you a discount.
Thanks
But
If you succeed in getting Yi Zhao to eat you, you have to tell me
Only then can I fuck him.
Wrong
How about we play 3P?
Hey, let’s do 4P
Call that tall guy here too, damn it
That guy Li Yizhao is really attractive.
what is this
Ah, that
I really...really didn't intend to spread it
That guy Li Yizhao refuses to give my dad's house back.
I went to the real estate agent and asked about it.
There will be an update soon and you can get a lot of money.
That guy has nothing to lose
I couldn't threaten him. Then you just showed up.
I watched the way he looked at you...
Got it
Stable
Hello
When that guy was beaten, he didn't dare to move at all.
but he said
'This...'
'Destroy this'
'It'll be fine in a few days'
'Can you give me a few days to think about it?'
'Can you please destroy these photos'
Funny
Right
thank you for the medicine
I just want to thank you
I'm leaving
Idiot
Hello, is this the police station?
Xu Zhengyin is a fucking rotten person
I took so many photos. What a retarded thing.
Just because of these photos…
Will he just be beaten obediently?
When are you going to come back?
(One photo! Don’t get sick and stay healthy all the time)
(Teacher Yalu of Yidun Kindergarten stayed)
Yedon Kindergarten…
So he was born in your kindergarten, right?
You're like this and there's nothing anyone can do to you
It just made Yi Zhao Xin very tired.
Didn’t you say you haven’t seen each other for more than a month?
stay with me
I need a long, long time
Does it have to go to this point?
I…
I want to own your future
What would you do if he didn't show up?